https://biotium.com/privacy-policy/

user-1
BACKTech Tips & ProtocolsBrochure LibraryProduct Safety ReportsPublications & Highlighted CitationsFrequently Asked Questions (FAQs)Special OffersNew Lab Startup ProgramBACKAbout UsCareersContact UsThe Full Spectrum BlogOur TeamBACKProduct Protocols & SDSStorage, Shelf Life & ShippingContact Technical SupportBACKAntibody FinderFlourescence Spectra ViewerBACKOrdering InformationQuick OrderFind a DistributorContact Customer SupportBACKAnti-Epitope Tag & Anti-Biotin AntibodiesAnti-Human ImmunoglobulinCF® Dye Labeled & Biotinylated Secondary AntibodiesCF® Dye Single Label Conjugates for STORMHRP ConjugatesR-PE & APC Labeled AntibodiesStreptavidin ConjugatesBACKNitric Oxide (NO) DetectionNitric Oxide (NO) DonorsNitric Oxide Synthase InhibitorsReactive Oxygen Species IndicatorsBACKAmine-Reactive DyesAzide, Alkyne, BCN, Tetrazine & TCOBiotinylation ReagentsDyes For Labeling Carbonyls & CarbohydratesDyes With an Amine GroupFree DyesThiol-Reactive DyesTyramides and Tyramide Signal Amplification KitsBACKDNA Binding DyesDNA Quantitation KitsLabeled NucleotidesNucleic Acid Gel Stains & Related ProductsDNA/RNA Purification KitsqPCR ReagentsReactive DNA/RNA Binding DyesBACKBacterial ViabilityFluorescent Gram StainsMicrobiology Primary AntibodiesOther Bacterial StainsViability PCR ReagentsYeast StainsYeast ViabilityBACKNear-IR CF® Dye Annexin V ConjugatesNear-IR Cytoplasmic Membrane StainsVivobrite™ Rapid Antibody Labeling Kits for Small Animal ImagingBACKLuciferase SubstratesNucView® Caspase 3 SubstratesOther Enzyme SubstratesProtease SubstratesBACKCell Surface & Membrane DyesCytoskeletal StainsCytosolic TracersDNA/RNA Dyes & Nuclear StainsDyes for Mitochondria & Other OrganellesMembrane Potential & Nerve Terminal DyesReceptor/Ion Channel Toxins & ProbesBACKApoptosis AssaysProliferation & Viability AssaysBACKCF® Dye Protein Labeling KitsMix-n-Stain™ Antibody Labeling KitsMix-n-Stain™ Small Molecule Labeling KitsVivoBrite™ Antibody Labeling KitsBACKAuthorized DistributorsCareersContact UsBACKOrder SupportToolsTechnical SupportCompanyProduct ResourcesBACKView All CategoriesAntibody & Protein Labeling KitsApoptosis & Viability AssaysBuffers & AccessoriesCalcium Indicators & ChelatorsCell & Organelle StainsChloride, pH, Zinc & Other IndicatorsEnzyme SubstratesFlow Cytometry Accessory ProductsFluorescent Proteins, Nucleotides & Other ConjugatesIn Vivo ImagingLuciferase Reporter Gene AssaysMicrobiologyPCR & Molecular BiologyPrimary AntibodiesProtein Detection & AnalysisReactive CF® Dyes, Other Reactive Dyes & Biotinylation ReagentsReagents for Nitric Oxide (NO) & Reactive Oxygen Species (ROS)Secondary Antibodies, Anti-Tag Antibodies, & Streptavidin ConjugatesBACKCategoriesNew productsSpecial offersFAQProducts from A to ZBACKProductsTechnologiesSpecial OffersSupport & ResourcesCompanyLog InFluorescence Spectra ViewerAbout Us
BACK
Nucleic Acid Gel Stains
PCR & DNA Amplification
DNA & RNA Quantitation Kits
Immunofluorescence Microscopy
Cell Viability & Apoptosis
Cellular Stains
CF® Dyes
Product Resources
Frequently Asked Questions (FAQs)
Tech Tips & Protocols
Brochure Library
Product Safety Reports
Publications & Highlighted Citations
Special Offers
New Lab Startup Program
+1
Skip to content
View
CDX2 / Caudal Type Homeobox 2 Monoclonal Mouse Antibody (CDX2/2214)
Sizes: 50 uL, 100 uL, 250 uL, 500 uLCatalog #: BNCAP2214-100, BNCAP2214-500, BNCA2214-250, BNCB2214-100, BNCB2214-500, BNC062214-100, BNC062214-500, BNC052214-100, BNC052214-500, BNC042214-100, BNC042214-500, BNC882214-100, BNC882214-500, BNC142214-100, BNC142214-500, BNC432214-100, BNC432214-500, BNC552214-100, BNC552214-500, BNC682214-100, BNC682214-500, BNC942214-100, BNC942214-500, BNC402214-100, BNC402214-500, BNC472214-100, BNC472214-500, BNC602214-100, BNC602214-500, BNC612214-100, BNC612214-500, BNC802214-100, BNC802214-500, BNC812214-100, BNC812214-500, BNC002214-100, BNC002214-500, BNC702214-100, BNC702214-500, BNCH2214-100, BNCH2214-500, BNCP2214-250, BNUM2214-50, BNUB2214-100, BNUB2214-500,
- BNCR2214-250View allHide
View
CD28 Monoclonal Mouse Antibody (C28/74)
Sizes: 50 uL, 100 uL, 250 uL, 500 uLCatalog #: BNCAP0074-100, BNCAP0074-500, BNCA0074-250, BNCB0074-100, BNCB0074-500, BNC060074-100, BNC060074-500, BNC050074-100, BNC050074-500, BNC040074-100, BNC040074-500, BNC880074-100, BNC880074-500, BNC140074-100, BNC140074-500, BNC430074-100, BNC430074-500, BNC550074-100, BNC550074-500, BNC680074-100, BNC680074-500, BNC940074-100, BNC940074-500, BNC400074-100, BNC400074-500, BNC470074-100, BNC470074-500, BNC600074-100, BNC600074-500, BNC610074-100, BNC610074-500, BNC800074-100, BNC800074-500, BNC810074-100, BNC810074-500, BNC700074-100, BNC700074-500, BNC000074-100, BNC000074-500, BNCH0074-100, BNCH0074-500, BNCP0074-250, BNUM0074-50, BNUB0074-100, BNUB0074-500,
- BNCR0074-250View allHide
View
View All New Products
New products
A - Z Search
ABCDEFGHIJKLMNOPQRSTUVWXYZ
View All Products
Products from A to Z
FAQ Categories
Apoptosis, Necrosis, and Cell Viability KitsCellBrite™ & MemBrite™ Membrane & Cell Surface StainsCF® DyesDNA Quantitation KitsDNAzure® Visible DNA Gel StainEvaGreen® Dye and Master MixesEverBrite™ Mounting Medium & CoverGrip™ Coverslip SealantGelRed® and GelGreen® Nucleic Acid Gel StainsGelRed® and GelGreen® troubleshootingIon Indicators & ChelatorsLuciferase AssaysMicrobiology: Dyes for bacteria and yeastMix-n-Stain™ Antibody Labeling KitsNucView® Caspase-3 Enzyme SubstratesOrganelle & Cytoskeleton StainsPMA and PMAxx™ for viability PCRProduct shipping, storage, shelf life, & solubilityProtein Detection & AnalysisResazurin Cell Viability AssayTrueBlack® Background ReducersAsk a question
FAQ
Special Offers
Quick Order Tool
Nucleic Acid Gel Stains
GelRed® & GelGreen®
|
DNAzure®
Gel-Bright™ LED Gel Box
Product Resources
Frequently Asked Questions (FAQs)
Tech Tips & Protocols
Brochure Library
Product Safety Reports
Publications & Highlighted Citations
Special Offers
New Lab Startup Program
Support & Resources
About Us
Spectra Viewer
AntibodyFinder
$0
Privacy Policy
Biotium, Inc respects your privacy. Our guidelines for protecting the information you provide us with during your visit to our web site are listed below.
Privacy Statement
This statement discloses the Internet Privacy Policy for the Biotium, Inc. website, www.Biotium.com. This site has been designed so that no personal identifying information is displayed online or is accessible to the general public. You can browse Biotium.com and our online catalogs without telling us who you are or revealing any information about yourself. To obtain access to special features such as pricing and ordering we ask that you register on our site.
Use of Data
Information collected during ordering process – When you order and register with Biotium, Inc. on the web, we collect the following information: name, address, phone, email, payment method including credit card numbers, and personal web settings. We do not sell or distribute this information to any third party except to complete transactions with our freight companies that drop ship orders on our behalf.
When you register as a customer and provide us with your email address, we will occasionally send you email with recommendations or notices of new products, prices, and services. Once you register, you will be given an opportunity to opt out of this service by changing the settings in your profile or via the first email you receive from us.
Information collected during promotional programs – Information may be collected from you via direct mail, electronic and internet campaigns as well as through e-newsletters, requests for literature and support, and customer surveys. When you respond to a promotional campaign, Biotium, Inc. collects contact information as well as additional information to help us qualify the success of a promotion and to determine eligibility. Biotium, Inc. will not sell or distribute names and mailing and email addresses and other contact information to third party advertisers except for the joint promotion of Biotium, Inc., and the third party.
Cookies
Biotium.com uses software tags called “cookies” to identify customers and track shopping baskets when they visit our site. This benefits the customer by allowing them to stay logged in during their visit so they do not have to continually log-in. It also allows selected products within a shopping basket to remain as a customer goes to other areas to browse.
Log Files
Biotium, Inc. maintains log files of the traffic that visits our site. We do not link any information gathered in these log files to personally identifying information. Log files are used to manage traffic loads and help provide reliable service, all with no association to your personal identity. Information collected includes IP addresses, browser types and pages visited.
Specific Customer Questions
Users who would like a response to specific questions concerning their service are directed to the Contact Us section on our web site or our customer support at 800-304-5357. We read and review all of our customer service queries and use the information contained therein only to resolve the question at hand.
Correct/Update/Delete User Information On Biotium.com
Users can update or correct, their personal information on Biotium.com by changing their profile information in “My Account”. Email communication preferences can be updated here. If you have any questions, e-mail our customer service team at order@biotium.com.
Removal from the Biotium Mail List
Email your request to marketing@biotium.com to be removed from our mail list.
Information Security
All information gathered on the Biotium.com site is stored and maintained in secure facilities. Our web site is regularly tested for potential security breaches. Our current security technology is Secured Socket Layer (SSL).
Biotium, Inc. reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time. The revised policy will be posted on our website for visitors to review.
Data Theft Contingency Plan
Biotium, Inc. makes every effort to ensure that data is secure. In the event that our processes fail to prevent the theft of sensitive data, we will undertake the following:
Customers that may be impacted by any data theft will be notified.
Notification that data has been compromised will be given to the vendor bank within 48 hours of obtaining this knowledge.
At the request of the customer, we will place on record the contact information for any impacted financial institution (i.e. credit card issuer) and notify the institution within the same time frame as given above.
We will communicate to the customer whatever information may aid their efforts to prevent data theft from causing harm to their organization. This may include an estimate of the number of records, users, or accounts involved.
Privacy Policy
Create a new list
